Wow. I didn't know you had a fan.
[BILLY] I feel a sense of…
Potential?
Have you seen my red shoes?
[PRECIOUS] You're becoming so forgetful!
First, you lost your keys.
Now, it's your shoes.
[BILLY] I got out of the car
holding my shoes.
[PRECIOUS] Then where are they?
[MALE OFFICER]
Carlos Toledo, you're free to go.
[CALOY] You two again?
Who bailed you out?
[CALOY] I don't know!
[JORDAN] A taxi arrived.
We don't know who it was,
but that person handed him an envelope.
[MARIELA]
You really take after your father.
[SCREAMING] Ma! Ma!
- Take her.
- Help!
Abigail!
[ABI] Luck is finally on our side.
I can feel it.
[SECURITY OFFICER]
Ma'am, who are you meeting?
Oh, I'm here for Ms. Billy. My idol.
LoveList's CEO.
Oh, LoveList! That's upstairs, ma'am.
- Oh, I can go upstairs?
- Yes, ma'am.
[SQUEALS] Oh my gosh!
Thank you!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[CHEERING, APPLAUDING]
[BLAIRE] Chief, excuse me.
Someone's looking for you downstairs.
But she doesn't have an appointment.
Who is it?
She said her name is Abigail Mercado.
[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
Hi, miss!
Are you Abigail Mercado?
Yes.
Let's go upstairs.
Chief Billy is waiting for you.
- Ms. Billy? My idol?
- Yeah!
Oh, okay.
It's beautiful.
So people tell me.
No, not you! I meant them.
- All of them here.
- Oh, you meant them?
Everyone here has a pleasing personality.
Oh, them?
No, all of us, actually.
- [BILLY] Could we add--
- Chief, Ms. Abigail is here.
- Hi, Abi!
- [SQUEALS] Ms. Billy!
- Ms. Billy!
- [BILLY] Hello, how are you?
- I'm great!
- Welcome!
Welcome to LoveList!
Yes, I'm finally here!
This place is amazing!
Your office is huge!
Thank you.
I mean, you got 323,000 subscribers
in just two years!
Your office is bound to look great!
And you even have 465,000 male hopefuls.
[SQUEALS] Sounds like you're
all having a lot of fun here!
Everyone, this is Abi.
Hello.
Hi, girl. I'm Toni.
- I'm the--
- Head of Finance!
Hmm. Hi, I'm Marj--
You're the Social Media Manager!
[MARJ CHUCKLES] Wow.
And there's Charm!
She's the Head of Design and Marketing.
I watch all your vlogs!
Hmm.
For sure, you know him too.
Wow! He's handsome!
You're Jordan Valentin!
He's the only one who
developed the LoveList app.
- Right?
- You're right.
And he's the
head of the IT department.
In case you didn't know,
he went to college in Australia!
He had a full scholarship!
And he has a bar in Pobla!
Jade and Jude's!
- Wow!
- Hi, I'm Abi!
- Nice to meet you, Abi.
- Nice to meet you.
[ABI CHUCKLES]
So, Abi, what brings you here?
Oh, I just happened to pass by,
Ms. Billy, because, well…
Didn't you say you would give me a tour
of your office when you had time?
Well, since I have time right now…
Do you have the time?
[BILLY] Ah!
Okay!
- Sure. I'll give you a tour.
- [SQUEALING]
Um, do you want anything?
We have coffee, juice, water?
- Anything!
- Wow, you have all of that?
Uh, I'll get some later!
Oh, but can I go to the restroom first?
Of course, of course!
- Please lead the way.
- Okay, ma'am.
Oh, you don't have to!
I know you're all busy.
I'll go by myself. Is it this way?
- Yes.
- All right, I'll go.
- Okay.
- He's so handsome…
So handsome!
- [ABI SQUEALS]
- Thank you!
- Oh…
- It's to your right.
- Right? Here?
- Who was that?
She was ogling you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
So?
Hmm…
I like her.
It's like she's got photographic memory.
You know, we can use it
on our presentations and all.
Mm-hmm. Plus,
she doesn't seem to be a diva.
- I kinda like her!
- Mm-hmm.
I think she's good.
She said she's a marketing graduate too.
She just couldn't apply
to other companies for now
because she's managing
her mother's internet café.
Hm?
Cat got your tongue?
[SIGHS]
It's kinda weird, right?
Look, Billy.
She gave you a call
during the launch of LoveLine.
For no reason.
Then,
she went to your house
uninvited!
It's weird!
And now she's here.
Unannounced.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
That's because she's a fan of LoveList.
Right?
It's obvious.
She keeps up with our subscriber count,
is knowledgeable about our operations,
and she knows about
our members' feedback too.
Maybe that's why.
Plus, she told me she's good
with the computer too.
Who knows? She could be of help to you.
[EXHALES HEAVILY]
The question is,
is she applying?
Seems not.
And the question is,
are we hiring?
Doesn't seem to be the case either, chief.
[OMINOUS MUSIC PLAYING]
Wow!
[WHISPERS] LoveLine…
[LAUGHS]
[OMINOUS MUSIC CONTINUES]
Billy?
I want some coffee.
Oh! I want some snacks too.
If it's possible,
can you get me
a slice of cake from downstairs?
And… by the way, Billy,
I don't like your work.
I don't like your attitude.
And most of all,
I don't like that face of yours!
So you are fired!
Where did that girl go?
What's taking her so long?
Oh, right.
Where is she?
Hi, Ms. Lindsay!
Our CEO, Ms. Billy, would like to know
when we can present
our investor packages to you.
[GASPS SOFTLY] Okay!
I will inform Ms. Billy.
Thank you for your interest
in investing in LoveList, Ms. Lindsay.
- Thank you.
- [ABI] Okay, okay.
All right. I know.
I'll give you a chance.
I can see your value.
Even if they can't, I can.
- So yes. I will give you a chance.
- [FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING]
- [STAFF MEMBER] Ms. Charm?
- Yes?
Sorry, something came up.
Okay. Coming.
Thank you!
Charm?
- Chief!
- Have you seen Abi?
Huh? N-No.
I went to your office just before,
and someone was there.
I thought you were in a meeting.
What?
Yeah.
Let's go.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
Abi.
Oh, Ms. Billy Idol!
I really look up to you so much!
Check out this award of yours!
"12th Annual Tech Achievement Awards:
Best Social Application."
This was the award you received
back in January, right?
- Mm-hmm. Yes, correct.
- I watched the livestream!
Plus, your gown was beautiful!
It's a long gown in emerald green!
You were so gorgeous.
[CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY] Thank you.
Have you been here for a long time?
Ah! Yeah…
I got lost after going to the bathroom.
Who were you talking to earlier?
Talking to?
Oh, no one.
I was just admiring the office.
Maybe you heard me singing some praises.
Ms. Billy's office is just too wonderful.
- Mm-hmm…
- I wasn't talking to anyone.
[CHARM CHUCKLES AWKWARDLY]
Anyway, chief,
I spoke with Ms. Lindsay.
I followed up with her
regarding our presentation,
and she said she'll get back
to us with her schedule.
Okay.
Thank you, Charm.
- Okay. Thank you.
- [LAUGHS LIGHTLY]
Mm-hmm.
[ABI LAUGHS]
Your office is so wonderful, Ms. Billy!
Thank you.
Oh! No way!
[ABI] Could it be?
It is! It's the Spirit
of Innovation Award 2026!
It's gorgeous.
I'm finally seeing it in person.
Oh, wait. I got it wrong, Ms. Billy Idol.
Emerald isn't the color
that suits you best.
It's champagne. That's perfect for you!
You looked absolutely stunning
in that gown!
It's… Oh!
And your speech was so moving.
It brought me to tears.
You said,
"I'd like to thank someone
very special to me."
"My younger brother, Oliver."
"Oliver…"
"Oliver, this is for you."
"You've been my inspiration
all these years."
- See? I've got it memorized!
- Mm-hmm.
[ABI GIGGLES]
The genes we inherit from our parents
determine our characteristics,
like eye color, hair type,
and even certain health conditions.
That's right! Correct, Oliver.
Now, for my next question…
Why don't children look
exactly like their parents?
Similarly, why don't siblings look
exactly the same as each other?
You aren't the spitting image
of your siblings, right?
Who wants to try?
Uh… Biboy?
Uh…
Because…
Tsk! I don't know, ma'am.
[LAUGHTER]
[TEACHER] Don't-- Children.
Don't be like that.
Settle down, settle down.
- Ma'am, I know the answer.
- Yes, Oliver?
We don't get the same genes
as our siblings or parents.
Instead, we get
a combination of their genes.
That's why each of us is unique.
That's right! Correct again, Oliver.
Let's give him a round of applause!
[APPLAUSE]
[BIBOY WHISPERING]
That twig is such a show-off.
Why twig?
- He's skinny as a twig!
- Oh.
[BIBOY] I'll teach him a lesson later.
You keep saying that.
When will you actually do it?
Later. During recess.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Oliver really is my inspiration.
Everything I do here is for him.
Oliver sure is lucky.
Her sister loves him very much.
Of course.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
What kind of person
doesn't love their sibling?
Plenty of people.
There are plenty of people
who don't love their siblings.
Well, that's not the case with Oliver.
He's a kind boy, and…
he's very smart.
He definitely takes after
his sister. [CHUCKLES]
He's also a fighter.
His biggest battle?
Type 1 diabetes.
Diagnosed when he was 7.
That's why we put in extra effort
into taking care of him,
especially since Auntie Pres and I
are the only family he has.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
By the way,
where are your parents?
They're dead.
They're long gone.
[STIRRING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MUSIC STOPS]
Oh, so we're in the same boat,
Ms. Billy Idol!
I told you before, right?
I don't have a father.
My sister's gone too.
It's just my mother and me.
- Mm-hmm.
- It's funny.
Sometimes, I think about
signing her up for LoveList
- so she can find love again.
- Mm?
- [ABI CHUCKLES]
- And speaking of LoveList,
I promised you a tour, right?
Let's do it. Come on.
[SQUEALS] Right now?!
- Yeah. Let's go?
- Oh, okay! Let's go, idol!
[BILLY] Where do you want to start?
Oh, let's start here.
This is the LoveLine call center.
That's where we answer calls
from our members.
Usually, this area is very busy.
And then, over here,
that's our common area.
All the employees can get
free drinks from our café.
And the room you were just in,
that's my office.
[ABI] Yes, I figured. [CHUCKLES]
That's where all the magic happens.
That's where we discuss and brainstorm.
That's where we celebrate
small and big victories.
Up on the third floor,
we have our conference room.
Usually, we meet
with clients or investors there.
Sometimes,
we use it for special occasions.
Oh, you're really incredible,
Ms. Billy Idol!
You were able to build
such a big business!
Congratulations!
[BILLY] Thank you, Abi.
Do you think I could be part of LoveList?
Because I want to learn from you.
I want to be like you.
I mean…
Are you accepting applications?
Even just as your assistant.
I won't say no to that!
Sorry, but she already has an assistant.
And that's me.
Hi, I'm Blaire.
Nice meeting you,
even though you've been
ignoring me since earlier.
I didn't ignore you. I told you
your outfit was nice, didn't I?
Yeah, right.
Anyway, Chief, you have to sign this.
This is the billing
for the additional computers
that are coming.
I see. Sorry, Abi.
I hope you enjoyed our mini tour.
But I have to go.
I have a lot of work to do.
- Thank you for visiting.
- Of course!
I really enjoyed it.
Thank you so much for your time.
Thank you, Ms. Billy Idol!
- [BILLY] Thank you.
- [ABI GIGGLES]
- Take care, Abi.
- I will.
- [BLAIRE] Thank you.
- Thank you. Take care.
[CHUCKLES]
- Be safe.
- Bye, Abi!
Hm?
[BLAIRE] Anyway, chief,
I also need your signature here
so we can follow up with the bank
about the release of your loan.
[UNSETTLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[BILLY] Please do follow up with them.
My loan's already approved,
but they still haven't released the check.
[BLAIRE] No worries.
I'm sure it'll be released this week.
Thank you.
[GIGGLES]
[UNSETTLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Guys,
Chief Billy has already reviewed
our presentation for Ms. Lindsay.
And we have revisions to do.
Oh, I hope my crystals can convince
Ms. Lindsay to invest.
[INHALES SHARPLY]
But we're doing great, aren't we?
Right?
Of course, why are you even asking?
LoveLine has been well-received.
It translated to new members for LoveList.
We also have new ads coming in.
We have potential investors too.
It's just that putting up
a call center is very expensive.
[CHARM] And…
Billy mortgaged her house for it.
But Billy is positive that
she will recoup her investment.
[TONI] Think positive!
- Think positive.
- Well, well, well.
We're really going to recoup it if…
if…
no one spoils it.
[MARJ] We just said
to think positive.
- You're so pessimistic.
- We just said so.
[PHONE RINGS]
- Hold it!
- Okay.
There.
[MARJ] I think you need that too.
- [TONI] Hold it.
- Hello?
- Look up.
- Who's this?
[LARRY] Hello?
This is Larry, the taxi driver.
[LARRY] I heard that you called
the office looking for me?
Yes, Mr. Larry.
Thank you for calling.
You said that you forgot
your wallet in my taxi.
[LARRY] But I didn't find
any wallets here.
Actually, sir,
I didn't call about the wallet.
I'd like to ask you something
about your passenger
last night at around 7:00 p.m.
in Tenement Road.
With how many passengers I drive,
do you think I'd remember that?
You will receive a reward.
You said seven last night, right?
Wait a minute.
[LARRY] Ah, I remember now.
The beautiful woman.
Your passenger was a woman?
Uh…
What did she look like?
Can you describe her to me?
Wait a second.
How much is the reward?
Five thousand pesos!
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
I remember what she looked like.
As well as where I dropped her off.
Okay.
Where can we meet?
Just meet me at our garage.
But you need to hurry up.
I still have stuff to do.
Okay. Thank you.
Wait a minute!
You're going to meet with him?
Didn't Billy tell us to stop already?
Here, Jordan. That's citrine.
It prevents misfortune.
So you won't get hurt.
Take a deep breath. Inhale.
[INHALES DEEPLY]
Exhale. [EXHALES DEEPLY]
- Inhale.
- Toni, Toni, Toni.
I don't have time for this.
But go on, just keep going.
Hmm? Where are you going?
[JORDAN] Uh…
Just out to get a coffee.
- Mm.
- Ahh.
[IN UNISON] Coffee…
Mm.
So, where are you going?
Fine.
I spoke with the taxi driver already.
He agreed to meet.
He'll describe the person
he dropped off at Caloy's house.
Chief, he said it was a woman.
- A woman?
- Mm.
[FOREBODING MUSIC PLAYING]
Okay, Jordan.
I know I was impulsive myself.
I admit that.
But this is a different story.
Didn't you get stabbed?
Maybe we need to let
the authorities handle this.
[JORDAN] Dude.
You know that won't achieve anything.
The authorities move so slowly.
It's just like with my mom's case.
Until now, no one has been arrested.
No one has been punished!
[FOREBODING MUSIC CONTINUES]
Okay, let's do
the circulatory system this time.
What organs are involved?
Heart, blood vessels, blood…
One more! I taught you this, right?
- One more! You can do it.
- One more?
Oh, I remember now! Lungs.
- Very good. You did great.
- [GIGGLES]
- Let's eat first.
- Okay.
Just don't forget those, okay?
[SUZIE] I have cupcakes. Take one.
Uh…
I'm not allowed to eat those.
My mom baked these for me.
I also requested one for you.
Low sugar, low carb!
- Wow, how nice of you.
- [GIGGLES]
So, which one is it?
[SUZIE] It's this one here.
Thank you. Are you sure?
- Sure!
- [CHUCKLES]
- Do you want us to share?
- Okay.
Here's yours.
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]
Mm! It tastes really good.
[BIBOY'S FRIEND] There he is!
Go, eat his food!
- It tastes good.
- There he is.
- Go, eat it!
- [SNICKERS]
- There you go!
- That's not yours!
- Is it delicious, bro?
- How selfish!
- [SNICKERING]
- Whoa!
[LAUGHING]
[OLIVER] Suzie, are you all right?
- [SNICKERING]
- Oh!
Twig is getting mad already!
[BIBOY AND FRIENDS] Twig! Twig!
That's enough!
Let's just leave, Suzie.
What? You're not fighting back?
Well, that's what you'd expect
from a twig! Twig!
[BIBOY'S FRIENDS LAUGHING]
- [GROANS]
- Ooh! He got hit!
- Nice hit!
- You're really good, bro!
- There you go!
- That's what I like to see!
You're really great, bro.
- [GRUNTS]
- Oh!
- Bro!
- Hey, bro!
Hey! What's going on here? Stop that!
- Are you all right, bro?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Jordan!
How can you be sure
the taxi driver will tell the truth?
I think he'll cooperate.
If not, I'll make him.
What if he's working with Caloy?
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
Billy, this taxi driver is
our best shot right now.
He's our only lead to the woman
who gave him the money.
[JORDAN] Whoever she is,
I won't let her ruin LoveList.
I won't let her do that to us.
To you.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC CONTINUES]
You guys are leaving?
Uh…
[VALERIE] Don't we have a meeting
to discuss our social media strategy?
Yes, we do.
Toni will lead the meeting.
Sorry, we just need to do something.
[VALERIE] Ah, where?
Sorry, Val. We're running late.
[JORDAN] Do you think it's her?
I don't think the taxi driver
was referring to her.
I know she can be scheming sometimes,
but I don't think she's the type
of person who'd conspire
with someone like Caloy.
- I hope so.
- [PHONE RINGS]
- We'll find out soon.
- Wait.
Hello?
Okay, I will.
Yes, ma'am. I'm on my way.
Oliver got into a fight.
- I'll just go to his school.
- Wait, Oliver?
Did he get hurt?
I hope not. They didn't tell me.
- I'll take care of it.
- Are you sure?
Okay then.
I'll meet with the taxi driver. Okay?
Be careful, okay?
You too.
[STIRRING MUSIC PLAYING]
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Good afternoon, sir.
I'm Jordan.
Where's Mr. Larry?
Oh, I'm sorry.
You missed him.
He just left.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- Okay, thank you.
- All right.
[CALOY] Boss.
Boss!
Are you Jordan?
Hey! What are you doing?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
If you say anything to that man,
I'll finish you off!
- Caloy!
- And your family--
Let him go.
[LARRY] If you have a problem,
don't drag me into it!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BILLY] What happened?
I got into a fight.
[MAN] Your brother
is a delinquent.
[BILLY] A kid defending himself
doesn't make him a delinquent.
[CALOY] You still haven't
learned your lesson?
Who's your boss?
Tell me!
Passing that checklist of yours
is an impossible task.
Huh?
I'd never put you in danger.
I dare you to show
your messages and calls.
[BILLY]
You are so stubborn!
Dude, I'm sorry.
You don't have to apologize.
You only did that for…
For us.
Aww!
[SOFT MUSIC PLAYING]